<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><!--	Introduction of IChing Game	Created by Hoa Truong on 2012-04-21.	Copyright (c) 2012 __MyCompanyName__. All rights reserved.--><ICHING>	<INSTRUCTION>		<IC>			<REALITY>				<![CDATA[Despite being the base of many known disciplines as Chinese Medicine, Tai-qi, Qi-gong, Taoism, Fengshui etc., IChing remains an exotic mystery, if not saying being misunderstood or misused as an superstitious temptation in many cases.]]>			</REALITY>						<HEXAGRAM>				<![CDATA[IChing-“The Book of Changes”- has only 64 hexagrams to answer any question asked. Due to it brevity, commonly our interpretation of the Oracle's answers are biased by our wishes or agenda while it's supposed to help expanding our awareness of the unknown. Through generations, interpretation from other interpretations has lead us far away from the simple truth: Ancient sages understand the matter of change, of associations and coincidences well enough to explain it in such this simple way.]]>			</HEXAGRAM>						<THISGAME>				<![CDATA[This app gives users a convenient and fun mean to cast I-Ching hexagrams to answer to any of your questions. To avoid the old track "interpreting from other interpretations!", it does not explain how to interpret in words the Oracle answers. Instead, it accompanies with several preparatory games, which are designed to make the fundamental phenomenon of Change becoming the base for users' intuition to expand. Eventually user would be capable to use one's own intuition to interpret answers from the Oracle appropriately. Just the several words to kick-start:]]>			</THISGAME>						<KICKSTART>				<![CDATA[+ Identify your knowledge or wishes on the matter you are about to ask the Oracle, but only to delimitate them when you interpreting his answer. The Oracle's answers exist independently with your rational mind. <i>Harmony is the atmost fundamental of IChing.</i><br/>+ Let the Oracle helps you listening to your own intuition in any decision. It's superstition having the Oracle dictates your life, but it's cleverness having the Oracle enriches your life with more possibilities.<br/>+ <i>Every single decision would possibly change your life.</i><br/>]]>			</KICKSTART>					</IC>				<LEVEL1>		</LEVEL1>				<LEVEL2>		</LEVEL2>		</INSTRUCTION>	<ICHING>